A world beyond imagination.
Under the Sea 3D is a documentary film directed by Howard Hall.
Imagine a world of incredible color and beauty.
Of crabs wearing jellyfish for hats.
Of fish disguised as frogs, stones and shag carpets.
Of a kaleidoscope of life dancing and weaving, floating
and darting in an underwater wonderland.
Now, go explore it!
Howard Hall and his filmmaking team, who brought you Deep Sea and Into the Deep, take you into
tropical waters alive with adventure: the Great Barrier Reef and other South Pacific realms.
Narrated by Jim Carrey and featuring astonishing camerawork, this amazing film brings you face to fin with Nature's marvels,
from the terrible grandeur (and terrible teeth) of a Great White to the comic antics of a lovestruck cuttlefish.
Excitement and fun run deep Under the Sea!
Narrator (voice), played by Jim Carrey.
3D films are motion pictures made to give an illusion of three-dimensional
solidity, usually with the help of special glasses worn by viewers.
3D films were prominently featured in the 1950s in American cinema and later experienced a worldwide
resurgence in the 1980s and 1990s driven by IMAX high-end theaters and Disney-themed venues.
3D films became increasingly successful throughout the 2000s, peaking with the success of 3D
presentations of Avatar in December 2009, after which 3D films again decreased in popularity.
Certain directors have also taken more experimental approaches to 3D filmmaking, most
notably celebrated auteur Jean-Luc Godard in his film Goodbye to Language.
The film explores themes of sea, australia, underwater, south pacific.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.